Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching.
Hallo! Sten! This time I'm joined by Yuna Ikuta from Morning Musume。 24 and Tako Inoue from Morning Musume。 24.
And my partner this time is Yuna Ikuta from Morning Musume。 24 and Tako Inoue from Morning Musume。 24.
Please bear with us until the end.
From July 13th, we will be holding the "Halo! Project 2024 Summer
All of Us Rega Altair has started!
Yay!
For the first time, it's All of Us!
How is it your first time to perform with 72 members?
No, it's just that the number of people I see in the mirror at rehearsal is about double what I saw at the last 3 of Us.
I'm going to be performing with twice as many people in the mirror as the last time I performed with 3 of Us.
I was worried that I wouldn't be able to stand out among them.
But I've practiced a lot, so I'll do my best to stand out from everyone else.
But there are really 72 of us.
I really want to shine.
If you don't take the initiative and do things on your own
I'll be buried in the crowd.
I'll do my best.
Yes, I'll do my best.
And with this tour
Do you have any theme that you want to show as Morning Musume。 Do you have a theme that you want to show as Morning Musume。
It could be from your own point of view.
I think the atmosphere has changed a lot since the last spring tour.
I was told by fans that the atmosphere had changed a lot
I was told by fans that the atmosphere changed a lot during the last spring tour.
They said I was very glamorous.
I was able to get that from the fans of other groups.
I hope that the fans of other groups
I hope the fans of other groups can feel it too.
I've been putting a lot of effort into it.
I'm getting more and more comments from them, and I personally don't usually get comments like that at the beginning of a tour.
I've been told to be cool for the first song and not to make anyone laugh.
I think this tour has been a great opportunity for each and every one of us to shine.
Project concert in my hometown.
We have prepared new songs for each group.
Project, so I'd like to do my best to create an opportunity for you to like the new songs of the other groups as well.
We will do our best to create opportunities for you to like other groups' new songs as well.
Now, please take a look at this video.
Please enjoy!
Thank you for watching!
hansome
A pinch is a spit.
Then will you come back? Come on, come on, come on...
Street corner music
Yoishira dancing
Colorful hair fluttering
You're so bad at dancing, but you're so cute
You're so confident
It's a good old day
When there's a mirror
Do it so
Hey!
Rumor of a love scene
Who's got what it takes
I love I love myself
Jet Gathering
Let's sing
The Best in the Universe
Happy Happy
I'm sorry
There's no end to the competition
There's no comparison between our hands
Cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha
Don't let me see you
Me and the time of yonbons
I'd like to be parted from you
come on, come on, come on, come on, come on
I'm going to be the best
I can't be strong
I'll fall apart
I am
I'm me, I'm me, I'm me
If we look at each other in the mirror
Wow
When you put on my rails
Today you're still in your best colors
I'm gonna switch it up
Be yourself, be beautiful, yeah
Ha
Rumor has it you're dazzling
Whoever it is, it's so
I love, I love myself
Seems to be a chain that gathers
The best in the universe
Happy, happy
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
No, I don't like the comparison.
It's not about the price.
Well, then, jan, jan, jan, jan.
Let's see what you got.
Me, myself.
I want other people to love me
Come on, now, all at once
I'm swinging
Wow.
Good job!
Morning Musume。 24's Rina Ikuta and
and Yumigetako from Morning Musume。
Yes, here we go.
I would like to talk a little bit about each other.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly.
I'll do my best.
Let's do our best.
Thirteen months have passed since the unveiling at the Nippon Budokan.
What I think has become the strongest in a little over a year
The thing that I think has become the strongest in a little over a year now is radio calisthenics.
2024, the All of Us tile is currently underway, and what I'm looking forward to on this tour is seeing the red venue.
The first thing that comes to mind when I hear the word "summer" is plum blossoms.
The first thing that comes to mind when I hear the word "summer" is plums, so here's a fay from me.
I recommend Sugita Ume, a stand-up umeboshi shop in Soramachi, for your pickled plums this summer.
Voodoo!
And last but not least.
When you think of Morning Musume。 24, what word would you put in the word "___"?
Silver
What do you think?
I've been thinking about a lot of things.
Dried plums in the middle of summer
I have an image of you liking umeboshi.
But there's a specific dried plum here?
Yes, I do.
Sugita Ume, a very sour plum.
And it's sour.
It's very refreshing.
I think it's a delicious plum to eat in the summer
I think it is a delicious plum to eat with Soumen noodles in summer.
What is Sugita Ume?
What do you mean by "salty" or "sour"?
Is it salty or sweet?
Or sweet?
The most sour plum is called sour plum.
But it's not that sour.
It's a little like grandma's pickled plums.
Like grandma's pickled plums.
It's very addictive.
So... speaking of Morning Musume。 24...
Yes.
Silver
Silver.
What's this?
It goes back to the glare I mentioned earlier.
I thought it would be easiest to express it in terms of color.
I see.
Silver is by far the best color.
I thought it would be really cool if everyone danced in silver costumes.
The costumes for Heavy Gate were silver, too, right?
I'd like to wear a really sparkling costume.
Morning Musume。 Do you have a favorite costume?
Do you have a favorite costume? My favorite costume is the second blue costume from the spring tour, the one without the jacket.
I love the shape of my outfit, but it really fits the unit song that I performed.
I love the shape of my costume, but it really fits the unit song "Style on My Love," which I performed, and it makes me feel very confident when I wear it.
After the VTR, I had a question for Ms. Ikuta. STE." After the VTR, I asked Ms. Ikuta a question about the Halo!
Halo! Sta.
Morning Musume。24最強 August 14 onsign
Hello Project New Member Audition 2024
Hello Project, now in its 27th year, is looking for new members!
A path that every member of Hello Project has gone through.
It is an audition!
The important thing is to have the courage to take the first step.
We will do our best to support your first step!
This time, we will hold auditions in two categories
If you love singing, dancing, and Hello Project!
If you love Hello Project, you can audition in the Hello Project category.
And if you want to show off your skills and personality in addition to singing and dancing, you can audition in the "Hello Project" category.
BEYOND THE POTENTIAL Division!
Why don't you join us and make your dreams come true with Hello Project?
We are looking forward to hearing from you!
Haloste
Next, I would like to ask Ms. Ikuta a question.
Please do.
Today, July 24th, is the day that our 15th single
Do It Now" was released on July 24th.
In reference to the lyrics, where would you like to get a ticket to now?
If it were overseas, it would be to Korea.
If it were in Japan, it would be Fukuoka.
What is the key point of today's makeup?
Lately I've been using foundation.
I have been using a foundation for a long time, but I changed its color to a new white. What are you most interested in now?
I wonder what I'm most interested in now.
Do you prefer sour or salty pickled plums? Sour? Or sweet?
If I eat umeboshi by themselves, I prefer sour, but if I eat them with rice, I prefer sweet.
What are three good things about the current 13-member Morning Musume。
The fact that the junior members are so energetic.
And the way they communicate with each other during rehearsals.
I don't know what I'm going to say at the end.
But I think it's the live performance.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
Three good things about the current 13-member Morning Musume。 24
The juniors are very energetic.
Yes, the juniors are very energetic. When I'm standing in this concert and I see the junior members are so excited, I have a lot of moments of "Ha! I have been standing in this concert, and when the junior members are so excited, there are so many moments when I am like, "Ha!
I think it was probably a change in my awareness of how I should present myself, as I was getting more of the song assignments and so on,
I think it is a change in my awareness of how I should present myself, but I feel that people look at me more than before.
The second is the time of rehearsals and other times when I graduated from college.
There were times when we had to record a video, and they told us to finish the video in one session.
And then there were times when they would say, "Let's finish it the first time," and we'd finish it without making any mistakes.
I think it's good to see that everyone's pace has been set properly.
The last one is the live performance.
This is also connected to the glitz and glamour of the younger members, but it's something that can only be seen at that moment in the live performance.
Recently I've been seeing more and more things I want to see here and there in a song, so I think that's a good thing about the current 13 members.
I think it's a good thing that we have 13 members now.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
I'm Miyabi Natsuyaki, and this is Miu Ishii from Tsubaki Factory.
I don't cook very much, so today I'll do my best to cook.
What shall we cook this time? Today's dish is Hitsumabushi with eel. Hitsumabushi. Can you eat eel?
I've never had it. Really? Then it's a bit more of a challenge.
Grilled or something. It doesn't sound too scary.
I think it's pretty good.
So, where do we start this time?
Okay, now we're going to grill the eel.
Cut it into thirds so that it's easy to grill, and then grill it.
This is going in, isn't it?
This will make it even more delicious.
I'm looking forward to it.
First of all, let's put the eel on top before we light the fire.
Let's put the small one on top, and put these two on the side like this.
Let's put them on the side like this.
Here is the Miyabi-zu point!
Steam the eel with cooking sake! Here it is!
Yes, sir!
It's already cooked, so you can eat it.
You can eat it with a lentil wrench if you heat it up.
But, by steaming the eel, you can make it more fluffy.
After making it fluffy, add the sauce.
After making them fluffy, we put in the sauce to make them browned and aromatic.
It's a two-step process.
That's great!
Now, since we're not going to fire it up, I'd rather just sit back and watch, but...
We're going to sing a song, and then we're going to turn up the heat.
I'm sure you've already done a concert or something.
But before that, there are rehearsals and recording.
I'm sure you've already done concerts, but before that, you have to do rehearsals and recordings.
I'm sure this is the first time in your life that you've recorded a song.
How was it? How was it?
I was really nervous when I arrived and didn't really know how to record.
I thought they would use the investment after I sang the first song.
And then I'd look at the A melody, and then we'd split it up.
It was fun.
That's great.
I've never even tried to memorize a song.
How am I supposed to learn it? I was like...
When I'm singing at home, my voice is fine.
When I'm singing at home, my voice comes out, but when I go into the studio, I'm so nervous, I can't even speak.
Have you ever had that?
It happened a lot.
Yes, you did.
I can't speak, even on high notes.
What? You've been practicing? Today.
You were practicing.
Yes, I was.
I'm amazed that you can say you had fun.
I didn't have fun at all. I was too nervous. It wasn't fun.
It was like trying really hard to read the lyric cards. I wrote a lot of details.
Do you do that? I write.
I would write, but I didn't know what to write, so I circled or marked the parts I wanted to sing more strongly.
After I'm done, I look at other people's hair, and they're writing in more spaces.
Slowly. You didn't know how to sleep.
I'm starting to understand.
I'm drawing it in a lot, thinking that a year from now it'll be different.
So I'm steaming it up nicely.
Aren't they so plump? Scarlet cucumbers.
Here's the decoy I made earlier.
Pour about one third of this over the whole thing.
A third of it. -About here?
It's back to normal. It's back to normal.
Put some more sauce on the bottom and start grilling the bass.
But it burns quickly.
It's very dense. Low heat, very low heat.
It's not so much grilling as savory.
Okay, okay. So, here we go.
You can char it a little more, but it'll stick.
How's the smell?
how's the smell?
It smells great! It's super good.
It's really chopped up, so it's a little spoppy.
It's more fluffy now. It's got more height.
Okay, then, rice.
We put a lot of rice in the bowl, so instead of writing it down, we put it in a small bowl and eat it.
A little more golden rice.
It's fine if it's light, right?
Then put the noodles on top.
It's difficult!
This amount of eel is very strong.
Are you going to put all of it on?
Let's go.
Then, it's all covered.
Looks delicious!
I'm buying.
It's great.
You know, this is... this is the last of the seaweed.
Kelp tea.
Dried bonito stock.
Put this in.
To change the taste.
It's like ochazuke.
Great!
Now wait for it to boil a bit
And when it boils, we'll taste it.
A little sip here, a little nod there.
Even the nod is a decision!
If it doesn't taste too good, nod your head
Bon appétit!
Oh, it's hot!
Huff it a bit.
Oh, it's delicious!
Is it good?
Are you okay?
I'm just gonna put it in here.
And then we just need some condiments.
Let's put these three spices here and there.
Put the myoga in the middle.
Shiso leaves in the middle.
And this one here.
Boldly!
It's okay to say it boldly.
Finally, add some chopped nori seaweed.
You can go for it!
Go for it!
Yes, it's done!
Eel Hitsumabushi is ready!
How do you like it, Mihama?
I've never had eel before, so I'm really looking forward to eating it, and I enjoyed cooking it!
I'm glad.
I did my best to make it, so please try it.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
So fluffy!
So soft.
Is it sweet sauce?
Is it a little sweet?
It's sweet.
It's delicious.
There are several ways to eat hizamashi.
Yes, you can eat it with eel first.
Then, there are so many condiments.
You can have whatever you like.
Try them together.
Then you have tea.
Do you want to go for the beauty?
Do you want the beauty to go? A little lighter.
Yes, yes, yes.
This way.
Is it good?
It's delicious.
Did you like it?
You don't have to lie.
Is it really good?
It's amazing.
The onions are similar.
Yes, a little bit.
A little more unique.
A little unique.
It's delicious.
Good.
It's all kinds of things.
You can mix it with anything.
Or you can finish it with ochazuke.
Yes, ochazuke.
How do you like it?
I like it with spices.
You can put a lot of things in it.
Various things.
It has kelp in it. It's very delicious.
I think I like it best.
I like ochazuke best.
It's good.
It's delicious.
Some people don't have much of an appetite in the summer.
There are cold versions, too.
Ochazuke is good for that kind of person.
It's amazing.
So, you had fun making this dish?
It was a lot of fun.
Do you think you can make it at home?
I think I can do it if I try hard enough.
I hope you will try your best. Please come visit Hello!
Please come to Hello!
Thank you again. That's all for Hello!
Looks delicious!
Gorgeous!
It's amazing.
Wow, a cow of eel quality. What do you think? How do you like it?
I'm from Hamamatsu City, Shizuoka Prefecture, and I get so many eels that I've never bought eels myself.
Do you get eels?
I thought I was supposed to get them. I didn't know that. It's a dish I've been familiar with since I was a little kid, and I love it, so I want to eat it.
I don't live in Tokyo, but I have an image that eels are a bit expensive and I go out of my way to eat them on Saturdays, when it's beef day,
So I can't imagine getting them.
Is it normal in Hamamatsu?
What do you think of me, Grandpa?
You are rich.
No, not at all.
My grandpa loves fish a lot.
Oh, I see.
And because of that, he got a lot of great eels.
Let's put it that way.
No, that's not it.
I'll tell you what.
I cook a lot, and I'm raising the bar.
I've raised the bar so high, but somen noodles? I've been eating somen every day for a week.
I don't know if it's okay, but lately I've been raising the bar a little bit.
But I like Soumen... so I tried to make it like ramen, for example.
for example, if I wanted to make soy sauce ramen I'd make my own soy sauce ramen soup from scratch and add it to the ramen
And then I put the noodles in the soup, and then I put the somen noodles in the soup.
And it was really good, so I'm going to try it again on the empty side.
I often make stuffed peppers... for all my fans.
I've been thinking about putting a different spin on it lately.
But recently, I wanted to put a twist on it, and I thought it would be better with just green peppers.
So I made a tomato stuffed with meat.
And then I put cheese on it. Like hamburger cheese.
It tastes like hamburger cheese.
And then you put the cut up tomato stems on top, and it looks a little fancy.
It looks really beautiful, and I think I'd like to make it again because it's so delicious.
Also, since it's summer, there are vegetables, so it's good to eat tomatoes as a stuffing when they're good.
I often make boiled spinach and keep a lot of it in the fridge.
I also make that kind of thing.
The presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart
In this corner, we will present lyrics from Hello! Project's songs that have touched our hearts and talk about their charms.
Project's songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics. Project's songs and talk about their charms.
This week, I, Takashi Kitagawa, will be presenting.
Okay, here we go.
Ta-da!
Adults must feel like it's not fair or something. Adults want to go back to you.
So, Morning Musume.' 14's smiling you is the sun,
The lyrics of this song as a whole are very touching,
I thought the lyrics were very unusual,
I thought the lyrics were very unusual, like, "This is the only time you can enjoy your youth,
There are a lot of lyrics that say you only have this time to enjoy your youth, or that you should enjoy what you can while you still have it,
I'm sure it's not easy to go back...
It's not often that they say, "I sure wish I could go back to that time...", right?
That's what really hit me,
That's for sure.
I'd like to think so.
I mean, all the grownups tell you that you should have fun,
I do want to go back to that,
When I see middle and high school students having fun on the train, I think, "No, I want to go back,
I want to go back,
At the time, I wanted to become an adult as soon as possible,
I wanted to become an adult as soon as possible, so I thought it would be nice to be an adult,
I wanted to be an adult as soon as possible back then, but now I want to go back,
The lyrics of this song make me think that I should cherish every second of my life and live in the present.
There is also a lyric in this song that says to live a fair and honest life.
I always feel that way every time I listen to this song,
I always feel the same way when I listen to this song,
I always feel that it is okay to live life to the fullest in the present.
That is true.
The present moment can only be experienced in that moment.
This present moment,
age,
That's why,
I think that's why the song resonates so much in my teenage years.
I think Tsunku wrote the lyrics with the age range of the members at that time in mind,
I have heard that Tsunku wrote the lyrics with the age range of the members at that time in mind, and it is true,
It's amazing that the song has passed through the ages and is now able to appeal to our generation.
You have never performed it live? No, I have not.
I did appear at the Satsu-con concert of Mr. Sato, starting from the beginning of my impression, but I have never given a full performance,
I've never done a full performance, so I'd love to try it.
So, please look forward to the next installment!
Rina Ikuta of Morning Musume。 24 with Rina Ikuta,
Rina Ikuta and Takako Inoue of Morning Musume。 STE.
Morning Musume。 24 will release a new single on August 14.
It's a song for sentimental times, the best double A-side single.
Yay!
Yes! The song of a somewhat sentimental time is really something that Morning Musume。 The sentimental song has a feeling that has never been seen in any Morning Musume,
There are many solo parts by each singer,
It makes me a little sad,
But in the chorus, it's a very powerful song about a girl,
You know, the music video is really great,
Yes, they are all cute,
They are really cute.
It's really cute.
It's really different from the strongest one,
The music video is a great way to see the beautiful members of the group,
And the song itself is really, really cool.
Yes, and "Saikyou" is a song that gives you energy when you listen to it when you are feeling down. It's a very energetic song.
If you listen to the lyrics carefully, the last part of the second verse says something like "I want to be the strongest," so I think it is a song that can really cheer up people who are in the middle of working hard or striving toward a goal, so I really hope people from all walks of life will listen to it.
So this time, we will be looking at a new song by Morning Wesment Four from Hello Project 2024 Summer All of Us Vega.
Let's see the strongest! Yes, the strongest!
What do you think of the performance? I'm a singer, but "Saikyou" has a "hammory" at the end of the chorus.
There aren't many songs like that.
And to get the pitch of the harmonics right was a lot of work among the members, so we paid attention to making it beautiful.
I hope you'll pay attention to the beautiful hammoly.
The members really try to dance exactly as they should.
I hope you will also pay attention to this part of the song.
I personally would like you to listen to the fake performance by Mei Yamazaki and Rio Kitagawa right after the song starts.
This is where the strongest part of the song starts with the 15th term and the B melody is sung by the 17th term.
In the first and second chorus, it's a little like a sprout.
In the chorus of the last verse, after I sing, Ami Ishida sings, and so on.
In the chorus, after I sing the chorus, Ami Ishida sings the chorus, and there's an atmosphere of being united in a spirited way.
Please have a look.
Please have a look at it.
me
me me
Beautiful and hurtful
Lame powder layered on top of lame powder layered on top of lame powder layered on top of lame powder
I'll hide my haramatta
Let's go get the mustache
Lame powder layered on top of lame powder
shining jaramatta
My hands are absolutely killing me.
They might have noticed.
I'll be here when you are.
I'm sure you'll be along shortly for the ride.
I'm just me.
I'm kind of driving, aren't I?
I've got the strongest, most powerful body in the world today.
I'm tired of pretending to be weak, bye bye
I long to be alone, but you don't know me
Beautiful next Jaguar
Stop it!
Strongest sex!
Potty with a big hand!
Pretend to be an idiot.
We're gonna get through this and then we're gonna get stuck.
Expectations!
I can't keep up with you.
You can't love her any more than I can love you.
I always feel like this
The best babe breaker
I'm gonna do fashion, I'm gonna do fashion, I'm gonna do fashion, I'm gonna do fashion, Facebound
My Club Snake Song?
Only in hard times, stay positive, girl
Don't swear you're gonna leave me
Don't see me, lies and all
Lies and lines
But the truth is, I don't want you to hate me
Stop talking about the good old days and talk to somebody or something.
Where am I now? I have to scream.
I need a more powerful, more clumsy formal.
I'm in your debt, throw it down, and say bye-bye.
I'm in no hurry to throw it all away now.
I've chosen a sad future
The most powerful, the most clumsy, the most formal
I've been ridiculed and laughed at for too long
Today and forever Tonight and to the very end
I only can I do it
It's the strongest and it hurts
It's the strongest, it's the strongest, it hurts
Strongest, strongest
I just can't help it, it's the best
Best party
Good action, exactly Faith
The age of frustration is nexus.
Honesty is the future, I'm afraid.
A.B.A.C., cut and peeled for nothing.
What if it's unraveling?
Energy, energy, jaw-dropping, jaw-dropping, jaw-dropping, jaw-dropping.
Really?
My sister.
Hey, sleepyhead.
You're the strongest, the most clumsy potty I've ever seen.
I'm tired of this weak three.
I don't know if we'll find you lying there.
I hate you.
I love you.
Get out of my way!
Strongest, clumsiest potty.
You don't know what you're looking at. You'll get through this.
I don't even like you. I don't like you.
I love you more than I love you
I always do
I always do my dream
The best, am I wrong?
Ugh, patience, Kimi. No more.
Are you mad at me? Yeah, I'm mad.
It's too late. It's too dangerous now.
Don't get through. Don't scream.
Just like in your dreams
I'm having fun, I'm changing things up, I'm the best
I'm the best at changing things up, changing things up, changing things up, changing things up
I'm always telling my daughters
You're the strongest
Strongest
A little cares
I'm always rooting for you. Keep up the good work!
Morning Musume。 24's Rina Ikuta and Akiko Yumigeta present "Halo! STE. It's time to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement. s new singles, "Kind of Sentimental" and "Saikyou" will be released on August 14.
These two songs are really two different songs, one in black and the other in white,
The two songs are really two different songs with black and white costumes, and you can see various expressions of the members in the songs.
Yes, and Hello! Project 2024 Summer All Over Us Vega Altair is now being held.
Next up is Altair's performance in Sendai.
It has been a long time since we had a concert with all the members, so I hope you will come and see it.
I hope you will be able to come and see it.
And on July 28th, we will be performing at the Takamatsuri Summer Boost.
This is, you know,
I, Erina Ikuta, will perform the ceremonial pitch before the game between the Fukuoka Softbank Hawks and the Orix Buffaloes.
Thank you very much. It is my first time and I am nervous, but I will do my best. After the game, there will be a special live performance by Morning Musume・24, so please come and join us. Please come and join us.
Yes, we are going to perform at Rockin Japan Festival 2024 in Hitotinaka on September 22nd.
It has been a long time since I have performed at Rockin' in Hitotchanaka, so it will be a first time for me. I will do my best in the heat. We hope you will come and see us.
I hope you will come to see my performance. Hello Project New Member Audition 024 is now open. Applications will be accepted until 10:00 a.m. on September 2nd.
For more information, please check the Hello Project audition website. Thank you very much.
Hello Stemmer!
This is a channel where Hello Project members will appear more and more. New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please give us a high rating, leave a comment, and subscribe to our channel.
This time we are joined by Rina Ikuta from Morning Musume。 24, and Ako Yumigeta. Bye bye!
Thank you for watching.